{
    "subject": "resource/Feline_Frame-Up",
    "predicate": "property/distributor",
    "object": "resource/Warner_Bros._Pictures",
    "human_readable": "Feline Frame-Up was distributed by Warner Bros. Pictures.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9854124188423157,
            "question": "Is 'Feline Frame-Up' a film produced by Warner Bros. Pictures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7855097651481628,
            "question": "Who distributed the movie 'Feline Frame-Up'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7195402383804321,
            "question": "What is the name of the film distributed by Warner Bros. Pictures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6451658606529236,
            "question": "What other movies might Warner Bros. Pictures have distributed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6336542963981628,
            "question": "Name a movie distributed by Warner Bros. Pictures."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5425881147384644,
            "question": "What type of company is Warner Bros. Pictures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5248141884803772,
            "question": "When was 'Feline Frame-Up' likely released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45482832193374634,
            "question": "Does Warner Bros. Pictures distribute only movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40444138646125793,
            "question": "What genre is likely the film 'Feline Frame-Up'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3889448344707489,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors in 'Feline Frame-Up'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Feline Frame-Up was distributed by Warner Bros. Pictures.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1173_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is likely the film 'Feline Frame-Up'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1173_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Warner Bros. Pictures distribute only movies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1173_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was 'Feline Frame-Up' likely released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1173_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1173_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1173_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1173_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1173_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1173_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1173_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1173_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1173_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1173_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1173_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Feline Frame-Up is a 1954 Warner Bros. Looney Tunes animated short film\" and provide information about its distribution by \"Warner Bros. Pictures.\" Therefore, the statement that Feline Frame-Up was distributed by Warner Bros. Pictures is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}